Guide to the James Lapine Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- May 2006 Acquisition, 1974-2006; Series I; 49.25; (53 boxes)
  - Audiovisual Material
    - Videocassettes
      - Anne Frank ( The Diary of Anne Frank ), "Just A Diary", 1986; YCALMSS715_0001; 1; 00:26:43; There is some static in the audio. PAL. Version YCAL MSS 715_0002 is better in quality. (Box 47, Item barcode 39002102417889)
      - Anne Frank ( The Diary of Anne Frank ), "Dear Kitty", undated; YCALMSS715_0002; 1; 00:26:43; This version is better than YCAL MSS 715_0001, the PAL version. (Box 47, Item barcode 39002102417897)
      - Anne Frank ( The Diary of Anne Frank ), "The Anne Frank House: A House with a Story"(duplicate), undated; YCALMSS715_0003; 1; 00:28:29 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002102417913)
      - Anne Frank ( The Diary of Anne Frank ), "The Anne Frank House: A House with a Story", undated; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002102417905)
        This is a duplicate of YCALMSS715_0003.
      - Anne Frank ( The Diary of Anne Frank ), "The Attic: The Hiding of Anne Frank", 1992; 1 (Box 47)
      - Into the Woods, Performance 2 - Act 1, 1989 May 24; YCALMSS715_0004; 1; 01:24:08 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002102417921)
      - Into the Woods, Performance 2 - Act 2, 1989 May 24; YCALMSS715_0005; 1; 01:28:09; The sound is extremely soft on this tape. (Box 47, Item barcode 39002102417939)
      - Into the Woods, Performance 3 - Act 1, 1989 May 25; YCALMSS715_0006; 1; 01:26:39 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002102417947)
      - Into the Woods, Performance 3 - Act 2, 1990 March 14; YCALMSS715_0007; 1; 01:12:12 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002102417954)
      - Into the Woods, Act II, undated; YCALMSS715_0008; 1; 01:01:46; The video is very grainy. It may be a multiple generation dub. (Box 47, Item barcode 39002102417962)
      - Into the Woods, Commercial - "Grimm Reality", 1987 October 6; YCALMSS715_0009; 1; 00:01:40 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002102417970)
      - Into the Woods, Commercial - "Grimm Reality Revised", 1987 October 7; YCALMSS715_0010; 1; 00:01:23 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002102417988)
      - Into the Woods, "Giant Hit", 1988 January 13; YCALMSS715_0011; 1; 00:01:15 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002102370575)
      - Into the Woods, Music Theatre International Conversation Piece, 1990; YCALMSS715_0012; 1; 00:59:51 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002102370583)
        Conversation between James Lapine and Stephen Sondheim. An author's video guide to producing Into the Woods.
      - Luck, Pluck and Virtue, rehearsal, undated; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612891)
        Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Passion, Matt Bogart, audition tape, undated; YCALMSS715_0013; 1; 00:21:34 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002102370591)
        A typewritten accompanying the tape reads: Dear James, Herewith Matt Bogart's tape of the Lodovicio and Giorgio scenes, plus songs. I've cued it up to the best scene only because the sound quality is horrendous on the first two scenes. Also, please keep in mind that he didn't have much time with material because of his performance and rehearsal schedule. He feels he can do much better in person. Please let me know your thoughts. Sincerely, Victorria Johnson.
      - Passion, Bruce McGill, musical audition tape, undated; YCALMSS715_0014; 1; 00:05:02 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002102370609)
      - Passion, Los Angeles, 1994 January 18; YCALMSS715_0015; 1; 00:17:59 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002102370617)
      - Passion, Con O'Neil, audition tape, 1994 January 5; YCALMSS715_0016; 1; 00:17:16 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002102370625)
      - Passion, [unlabeled and unidentified], undated; YCALMSS715_0017; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002102370633)
        This is a blank tape. It has not been digitized.
      - Sunday in the Park with George, Part 1 of 3 Cut 1, Part 2 of 3, Part 3 of 3, 3 parts tied, 1985 November 14; YCALMSS715_0018; 1; 02:24:17; A timecode runs throughout the tape. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002102370641)
      - Sunday in the Park with George, Reel #1, Michael Brandman Productions, 1986 January 12; YCALMSS715_0019; 1; 02:31:38 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002102370658)
      - Sunday in the Park with George, Acts 1 and 2, VIS TC in Picture, Michael Brandman Productions, 1986 January 13; YCALMSS715_0020; 1; 02:17:57 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002102370666)
        This tape begins with an intro to Sunday in the Park with George, but it then it cuts to a program on architect Philip Johnson, then various other programming including a "60 Minutes" segment and a baseball game.
      - Sunday in the Park with George, Acts 1 and 2, 2 acts tied, Michael Brandman Productions, 1986 January 15; YCALMSS715_0021; 1; 02:37:10 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002102370674)
      - Sunday in the Park with George, Acts 1 and 2, 2 acts tied (duplicate?), Michael Brandman Productions, 1986 January 15; YCALMSS715_0022; 1; 02:33:57 (Box 63)
        Restricted fragile material.
        This appears to be a duplicate copy.
    - Compact discs
      - Hunchback ( Der Glockner von Notre Dame ), 1998 (Box 48)
      - Passion, 1994 (Box 48)
      - Muscle, 2001; (2 discs) (Box 48)
    - Audiocassettes
      Boxes 49 and 50 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Faust, by Randy Newman, 1992-1994; (12 audiocassettes) (Box 49)
        - "Martha", master, undated; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612701)
          Contents include: "Life Has Been Good to Me" and "Feels Like Home to Me"
        - song: "Hard Currency", master, undated; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612719)
        - Workshop Presentation - Act I, 1994 December 9; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612727)
        - character: "The Lord", master, undated; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612735)
          Content includes: "Glory Train", "Northern Boy" and "Relax, Enjoy Yourself"
        - Randy Newman's Faust, new demos, undated; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612743)
          A list of contents is included with this audiocassette.
          It's a Damn Fine Day
          March of the Protestants
          When Love is in the Air
          Relax, Enjoy Yourself
          I Wanna Be a Gangster
          Happy Ending
        - Master, new demos, undated; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612750)
        - "Margaret", master, undated; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612768)
          Contents include: "Gainesville, Fl" and "Sandman's Coming"
        - "The Devil", master, undated; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612776)
          Contents include the song: "Northern Boy"
        - Workshop Presentation, Act Two, 1994 December 9; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612784)
        - "Faust", master, undated; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612792)
          Contents include: "Bless the Children" and "The Man"
        - Demos, 1992 March 24; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612800)
          Pass On Over
          How Great Our Lord
          Each Perfect Day
          Best Little Girl in the Whole Darn Town
          It Was Beautiful
          Bless the Children of the World
          Damn Fine Day
          Little Island
          The Man
          Love Time
          My Hero
          Life has Been Good to Me
          Hard Currency
          Gainesville, Fla
          Sandman's Coming
          Basin St.
        - Edited Master, undated; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612818)
          Pass On Over/Glory Train
          Best Little Girl
          Northern Boy
          Bless the Children
          Gainesville, Fl
          Relax, Enjoy Yourself (Pt. 1)
          Relax, Enjoy Yourself (Pt. 3)
          Relax, Enjoy Yourself (Pt. 4)
          Life Has Been Good to Me
          I Gotta Be Your Man
          Feels Like Home
          Bleeding All Over
          Can't Keep a Good Man Down
          Happy Ending (Demo)
        - Luck, Pluck + Virtue; Sound Cues
      - Luck, Pluck, and Virtue, 1993-1995 (Box 49)
        7 audiocassettes
        - Sound cues, 1993 Summer; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612826)
          Contents include: "Merry State" (clean and out-of-tune vocals, piano only), trombone, and cocktail music
        - Piano cues, 1993 August 28; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612834)
        - NYC Production, piano only and vocals, 1995; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612842)
          A list of selections and cues are included with this audiocassette.
          Overture
          Father
          Lester Running Out
          Whipple
          Follow Your Heart
          Betty
          Fight Music
          Train (a, b, c)
          Policeman
          Judge, Prison, Demcheck
          Whipple in Prison
          Mother
          Transition to Audition
          "Merry State" (Lester)
          Next!
          Hooker Music
          Hooker (continued)/exit
          Transition to Eye Clinic
          Transition to Englishman
          Whipple entrance
          Lancaster Hotel
          Eye Promotion
          Revival
          Crime/Whipple speech
          Judge #2
          Calendar Girl
          Meeting Betty
          Betty & Lester
          (cue 21 "Shaye vocal" is on side B)
          "Salve" underscore
          "Salve" chorus
          Montana
          Heart Like a Rock
          Grace
          Campsite
          Damsel in Distress
          Scalping
          Hospital scene
          Wheelchair
          Knocks
          Sonny Gordon's entrance
          Betty/House & Garden
          Montage
          Cocktail piano
          Transition to film set
          Lester's house
          Film underscore
          Bus Stop
          County Home
          The Park
          Dream #1
          transition
          Dream #2
          Curtain Music
          "Merry State" (Dream #2) end, ensemble vocal
          "Merry State" (Dream #2) including dialogue
          "Salve" Shaye vocal, a capella
          "Salve" chorus vocal
          "Merry State" Lester vocal
        - NYC Production, piano and vocals, 1995; 1
        - Score - La Jolla, 1993; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612867)
        - NYSF Benefit, 1992 May 13; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612875)
        - Piano cues, master, 1993 August 28; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612883)
      - Muscle, 1995; (13 audiocassettes) (Box 49)
        - Reading, undated; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612909)
        - Informal reading of script, tape 2, 1995 October 26; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612917)
        - Act I + II - partial, runthrough, 1995 November 17; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612925)
        - Finale+, 1995 November 21; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612933)
        - Act I, 1995 June 30; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612966)
        - Act I, 1995 June 30; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612982)
          This audiocassette appears to be a duplicate.
        - Act II, 1995 June 30; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612941)
        - Act II, 1995 June 30; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612958)
        - spec demo/two songs, 1994 February; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612974)
        - spec demo/two songs, 1994 February; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104613014)
        - Act II - runthrough, 1995 November 16; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104612990)
        - Workshop, judges and finale - versions 1 and 2, 1995 November 13-16; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104613006)
        - Act II; finale, November 17; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104613022)
      - II.8, undated; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104613030)
      - Elmer Gantry, 1996; (16 audiocassettes) (Box 50)
        - Act I, Part I, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613055)
        - Act 1 (Pt 2), Act 2, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613063)
        - Act 2 - last tape, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613071)
        - Songs, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613089)
          There is a list of songs included with this audiocassette.
          Riders on the Road
          Between Trains
          Shine
          Saved
          You Don't Know Who I Am
          On the Road
          Night Heat
          When Jesus Calls the Play
          No Greater Love
          He's Coming Back
          With You
          Nothing but the Blues
          The Wellspring
          Whatever Happened?
          Get Her Back
          With this Ring
          Finale
        - Score, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613097)
        - Reading, Act One, 1996 September 16; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613105)
        - Reading, Act Two, 1996 September 16; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613113)
        - James' Tape from reading, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613121)
        - Act One, Pt. 2 - Act Two, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613139)
        - Act II, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613147)
        - Songs, Acts I and II, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613154)
        - Falsettos movie, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613162)
        - Falsettos movie, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613170)
        - Act Two, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613188)
        - Act One, Part I, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613196)
        - Songs, Acts I and II, office copy, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613204)
      - Into the Woods, undated; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 50)
        - London Version, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613212)
        - Original (USA), undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613220)
      - Passion, 1993-1994; (10 audiocassettes) (Box 50)
        - Run Through, Tape 2, 1993 October 9; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613238)
        - Run Through, Tape 1, 1993 October 9; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613246)
        - Selections, 1994; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613253)
          This audiocassette was given to Tony voters in advance of the awards. It includes: Scene 1 - Opening, "Fosca's Letter", and "Loving You".
        - Tape 1, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613261)
        - Tape 2, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613279)
        - Selections from the Broadway Cast, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613287)
          Contents include: Scene 1 / Opening, "Fosca's Letter", and "Loving You"
        - Music only compiled from workshop tape, 1993 October 9; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613295)
        - Live recording of entire Broadway performance, cassette 1: top of show through park bench, 1994; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613311)
          A note is included with this audiocassette. It reads: This recording was made through the sound system for the purposes of planning the cast album. The recording was made during previews and it was, we believe, the final performance of Bill Duff Griffin as the doctor. In any case, it was around this time. It remains a record of the show during the preview period.
        - Live recording of entire Broadway performance, cassette 2: park bench through end of show, 1994; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613329)
        - Dialect intro. discussion with Debra Hecht; Finales, 1994 February 10-April 19; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613337)
      - Loving You, undated (Box 50)
        - demo, given to Lapine by Sondheim, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613303)
      - Twelve Dreams, 1982; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 50)
        - Allen Shawn: Incidental music, NY Shakespeare Festival, 1982; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613345)
        - Run Thru, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613352)
      - I'm Breaking Down, only copy, undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613360)
        Contents include "I'm Breaking Down"
      - Golden Child, music cues, 1998 February 4; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104613378)
        The Soul Shall Soar
        Hearts of Angels
        Divine Rain
        Fate's Embrace
        Prisms of the Heart
        First Kiss
        Seduction
        Energy Flow
        Soul Shall Soar
  - Oversize
    - Faust, musical scores and two t-shirts, undated; 2 (Box 51)
    - Faust, musical scores, undated; 2 (Box 51a)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 52)
    - Falsettos, musical scores, 1995; 2 (Box 52)
    - Into the Woods, musical scores, 1995 (Box 52)
  - Computer media
    - MicroVision FORMATTED 7-26-98 ToughGirl 1 7/26 7/29 3 7/26 7/29 Final 4 7/30 5 7/28, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0001; 1 (Box 53)
      Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - FAUST Back-up Disc Amended: 12/9/94 Version (1/6/94), 2006-ycal-0531-i-0002; 1 (Box 53)
    - Muscle 6/25/95, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0003; 1 (Box 53)
    - Muscle Back-up Disk Updated: 12/1/95, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0004; 1 (Box 53)
    - 10-26-95 MUSCLE SCRIPT (AS OF OCTOBER 26, 1995) 1ST DAY OF WORKSHOP REHEARSAL, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0005; 1 (Box 53)
    - 11-21-95 MUSCLE SCRIPT (AS OF NOVEMBER 21, 1995) JUST PRIOR TO WORKSHOP, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0006; 1 (Box 53)
    - MUSCLE Lapine Working Disk 11/29, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0007; 1 (Box 53)
    - MUSCLE SCRIPT as of 10-26-95 (1st day of rehearsal on 11/27/95-12/01/95 workshop), 2006-ycal-0531-i-0008; 1 (Box 53)
    - Hilly's Copy WHO'S ON TOP? June '98 6/15/98, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0009; 1 (Box 53)
    - MUSCLE Lapine Working Disk Updated: 12/1/95, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0010; 1 (Box 53)
    - GANTRY 4/10/96 (Gantry 10), 2006-ycal-0531-i-0011; 1 (Box 53)
    - "PASSION" ALL FILES (THESE DISCS CONTAIN ALL OF THE FILES ON "PASSION" FROM OUR MAIN DIRECTORY 6/13/95) DISC 1 OF 2, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0012; 1 (Box 53)
    - PASSION ALL FILES (THESE DISCS CONTAIN ALL OF THE FILES ON "PASSION" IN OUR MAIN DIRECTORY 6/13/95) DISC 2 OF 2, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0013; 1 (Box 53)
    - FOSCA Nov. 93 FINAL WORKSHOP VERSION, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0014; 1 (Box 53)
    - Passioné 5-1 11/1/93 FINAL VERSION OF WORKSHOP, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0015; 1 (Box 53)
    - "FOSCA" 1993 -SCRIPT PAGES WITHOUT LYRICS, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0016; 1 (Box 53)
    - Reading Script NYSF 6/92, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0017; 1 (Box 53)
    - MUSCLE REV. 10-13-94 FILE COPY!, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0018; 1 (Box 53)
    - MUSCLE 10/17/94 FILE COPY!, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0019; 1 (Box 53)
    - MUSCLE Version: Oct. 17, 1994 "FILE DISC" DO NOT USE FOR REVISIONS, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0020; 1 (Box 53)
    - MUSCLE 5/18/95 "FILE DISC" DO NOT USE FOR REVISIONS, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0021; 1 (Box 53)
    - MUSCLE 6/25/95 (FIRST REHEARSAL FOR READING), 2006-ycal-0531-i-0022; 1 (Box 53)
    - MUSCLE 6/30/95 FINAL VERSION FOR READING AT LINCOLN CENTER, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0023; 1 (Box 53)
    - LAPINE FAUST Working Copy FINAL VERSION OF WORKSHOP '94, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0024; 1 (Box 53)
    - FAUST Script ver.-11/15/94 JAMIE'S COPY, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0025; 1 (Box 53)
    - FAUST SCRIPT BACKUP of current copy 11/7, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0026; 1 (Box 53)
    - LUCK, PLUCK + VIRTUE -LA JOLLA PREVIEW; ALTERNATE ENDING 'A' ["VA"] (7/30/93) -LA JOLLA PREVIEW; ALTERNATE ENDING 'B' ["VB"] (7/29/93) -WORKING DRAFT (2/21/95) -MONTAGE (7/1/93) -1ST REH NOTES (6/22/93), 2006-ycal-0531-i-0027; 1 (Box 53)
    - LUCK, PLUCK + VIRTUE: -FIRST DRAFT, 11/8/91 -LA JOLLA PERFORMANCE DRAFT 6/28/94, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0028; 1 (Box 53)
    - LUCK, PLUCK + VIRTUE- -REVISION IN PROGRESS 11/30/94 -REHEARSAL DRAFT 2/25/95, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0029; 1 (Box 53)
    - LUCK, PLUCK + VIRTUE #1 REHEARSAL DRAFT (3/3/95) [REFORMATTED FROM 2/25/95], 2006-ycal-0531-i-0030; 1 (Box 53)
    - LUCK, PLUCK + VIRTUE PERFORMANCE DRAFT 4/7/95, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0031; 1 (Box 53)
    - LUCK, PLUCK + VIRTUE (Deb) A.D.'S DISC FROM LA JOLLA PRODUCTION JULY 1993, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0032; 1 (Box 53)
    - GANTRY10.DOC GANTRY10.BAK GANTRY10.CMP PLAY STY, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0033; 1 (Box 53)
    - GANT-MK1.DOC, 2006-ycal-0531-i-0034; 1 (Box 53)
- January 2009 Acquisition, 1990-2008; Series II; 7.21; (8 boxes)
  Arranged under two headings: Play Files, and Electronic Media.
  This portion of the collection includes correspondence, writings, notes, printed material, production files, research files, scripts, and other papers. Files have been left in the order in which they were received by the library
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 1079
  Box 61 (computer disks): Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Play Files
    - Fran's Bed
      - Drafts, 2001-2003; 13 (Box 54)
      - Drafts, 2003-2005; 16 (Box 55)
      - Play details, 2003; 2 (Box 55)
      - Drafts, 2003-2005; 18 (Box 56)
      - Drafts, 2004-2005; 19 (Box 57)
      - Rehearsal schedules, 2005 (Box 58)
      - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 58)
      - Casting, 2005 (Box 58)
      - Schedules, 2005 (Box 58)
      - Set Design, 2005 (Box 58)
      - Commentary and reviews, 2005 (Box 58)
      - "Fran's Bed", 2003-2005; 5 (Box 58)
    - "Spelling Bee" ( The 25th Annual Putnam County Spelling Bee )
      - "Thanksgiving Video", 2005 (Box 58)
      - "New York", 2006; 2 (Box 58)
      - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 58)
      - San Francisco & Chicago casting, 2005 (Box 58)
      - Costumes, 2005 (Box 58)
      - Scripts, undated; 9 (Box 58)
    - Shubert Organization correspondence, 2000 (Box 59)
    - Various correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 59)
    - Falsettos, 1994-2005; 3 (Box 59)
    - King Lear, 2007; 10 (Box 59)
    - Twelve Dreams, 1995 (Box 59)
    - Passione D'Amore, 1993; 2 (Box 59)
    - Passion, 1994-2004; 2 (Box 59)
    - "Public Theatre 50th Anniversary", 2006; 2 (Box 59)
    - Luck, Pluck, & Virtue, 1991 (Box 59)
    - Luck, Pluck, & Virtue, 1991; 2 (Box 60)
    - Into the Woods, 1990-2005; 3 (Box 60)
    - Correspondence for Into the Woods, 1990 (Box 60)
    - Stratford, Canada, Production of Into the Woods, 2005 (Box 60)
    - "Leonard Bernstein's New York", 1996 (Box 60)
    - "Ball of Fire", 2001 (Box 60)
    - "Babe", 1996 (Box 60)
    - "Big Street", 1998; 2 (Box 60)
    - "Dick Tracy", 1996 (Box 60)
    - "Groundhog Day", 1990 (Box 60)
    - "J. Edgar!", undated (Box 60)
    - "The Mechanics", undated (Box 60)
    - Max Lambert correspondence, 2005 (Box 60)
    - Charles Strouse songs, 2006 (Box 60)
    - "WATT?!?", undated (Box 60)
    - Chris Van Groningen correspondence, undated (Box 60)
    - "Feeling Electric", 2006-2007; 3 (Box 60)
    - "The Cheese Stands Alone", 1993-1994 (Box 60)
    - "Truly - Dance for Poland", 2004 (Box 60)
    - "Ideas for Shows", 2003, 2008 (Box 60)